{
    "id": "fc491b05d1334516a00978635f97c17a",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The thief jumped ........................ the wall.",
            "description": "Over is used to say on or to the other side of something high.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a59739bc3faa41808c142a49de93c977"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked ............................ the fields.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "in",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1619f1bdd53746249e377f5d66ba2746"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat .............................. her son and daughter.",
            "description": "Use between to talk about two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "amongst"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f94404bb0ee4250872b05620b82f4a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We drove ............................. the tunnel.",
            "description": "Use through for movement within spaces where there are things all around.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "in",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58fa5983bd224c6baeb5ccaf9a70d30b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you staring ............................. me?",
            "description": "Use at with look, stare etc.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c243a31a5d1d487b9ec40e97c397fa69"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took over a week to cross the Atlantic ............................... a ship.",
            "description": "We use on with bus, train, plane and ship.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b8d385e719e74602a2f0edf423e9d750"
        },
        {
            "question": "They live ......................................... the third floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4f95e1e2c62140059f1b900a533b5aff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that pretty girl .............................. the second row?",
            "description": "We use in a row.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4dca945aafc1453685bdb82e9475cf8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "London is ........................... river Thames.",
            "description": "Use on to show position on a line.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ba7fac75cae54bc1a5c08c6c1351e9ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should never run ............................... the road.",
            "description": "Across shows movement from one side to the other side.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "along",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "34b23582eaaf419b8fae38ee8a2cd64d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I first met him .............................. a department store.",
            "description": "In shows position inside. Use at with proper nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7292580e1ffb4ca49ae51fbd1813f294"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been ages ............................... I heard anything from her.",
            "description": "Use since with the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21a1b5b7cc924f63a68711485377cfdb"
        }
    ]
}